[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[theme music playing]
A LOVE OTHER THAN YOURS
[theme music concludes]
ALL PERSONS, LOCATIONS, RELIGIONS,
INCIDENTS, AND ORGANIZATIONS IN THIS DRAMA
ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS HAVE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER PARENTAL SUPERVISION
SCENES INVOLVING ANIMALS WERE FILMED
SAFELY WITH EXPERT ADVICE AND COOPERATION
-Marry me, Mi-do.
-[sentimental instrumental music playing]
Please, let's get… married.
[hiccups]
3. CAN WE FEEL THAT SPARK AGAIN?
[Mi-do]  The thought suddenly hit me.
If I broke up with Namgung,
how many books
would no longer be part of my life?
Could I really live
after losing all those dear books?
[sighs]
No.
[sighs deeply]
Could I really go on
living without Namgung?
[sighs]
[sentimental instrumental music continues]
[panting softly]
[sighs]
[pants]
[Suk-hee]  His name is Namgung.
Actually, he's the same age as Mi-do…
THE SORROWS OF YOUNG WERTHER
…and he'll be living with us
starting today.
Sweetie, you should say hello too.
What is it? Are you feeling shy?
[chuckles softly]
[inhales softly]
[music softens]
[music rises]
[mixer whirring]
[oven fire crackling]
Ah, it's hot! Hot, hot!
[Sang-hun] Excuse me, sir.
What are you doing?
-[Namgung] Hey, come taste this.
-Huh?
-[music concludes]
-[blows air, munches]
-[chewing] It's hot.
-[gasping, grunting]
[munches] Mm, mm.
What… What is this? I know this taste.
Corn Stick. Am I right?
They're discontinued.
Why are you making this?
[pan sizzling]
You all right? [exhales]
Hmm. [sniffs]
[pan sizzling]
Ah, jeez. Is she skipping again?
This is her father's memorial
and she decides to skip out?
Can you just dry that base already?
It's still completely wet, man.
I'm already doing it.
[pan sizzling]
[match strikes]
[Yeong-do blows air]
[grunts softly]
-[door opens]
-[bells jangling]
[Mi-do sighs]
EXORCISM CHRONICLES
-[cutlery clinking]
-[munching]
-Isn't that comic wrong for a memorial?
-[hiccups]
-Water, some water.
-Mm-hmm.
So, this is what Dad used to read, huh?
He used to put me in a stroller
and take me to the bookstore.
-He's making things up again, huh?
-You know it's true.
-I'm not making anything up.
-[both whisper indistinctly]
[Wan-do] I actually remember it.
But he also read
a lot of comic books, right?
[clears throat] So…
-there's something that I--
-[Yeong-do] That's nonsense.
Dad only ever read novels,
fantasy and martial arts.
Wrong, man. I remember it clearly.
-He looked really happy reading them.
-[Yeong-do] That's not true.
His favorite books were  Dark Mage,
-Dragon Raja,  and  Temple of the Dragon.
-[whispers indistinctly]
He was strictly a fantasy guy.
Hey, Mi-do, you remember that, don't you?
-We have something to say. [hiccups]
-No way. I remember Dad
at the bookstore reading comics
while pushing me around in the stroller.
Nah, you remembering
what you want doesn't make it true.
I know I'm right. He read those.
Mom, tell him I'm right.
[Yeong-do]
Dad only read novels, all right?
-So, we're gonna get married.
-[dramatic musical sting]
[quirky piano music playing]
Uh…
[vehicle whizzing past outside]
Uh… now I'm embarrassed with the abrupt…
-[exhales deeply]
-…well, attention.
[chopsticks clinking]
I remember Dad liked reading  Sunday Soul.
[gulps, hiccups]
[music concludes]
Do you guys remember…
when I was about three and a half…
years old, a dog lunged at Mi-do?
[Yeong-do] Namgung,
it's your fault he's like this.
You pushed him off a slide
when he was five.
He's been freaking weird ever since then.
We heard a scream of Mi-do,
and Namgung, he…
he left me with you
and ran straight toward her.
Wow. You should have let that dog get her.
Enough.
[chuckles] I'm joking. It's just a joke.
Anyway, I can still remember
that day so clearly.
The temperature, the smell,
the wind, the light.
Also… Namgung's back as he ran to Mi-do.
And I knew right there…
that one day you'd get married.
Just say it already.
Mom told you that, yeah?
-[gentle guitar music playing]
-Were you in love with her since then?
What? Dude, I was only like ten.
So, you've loved her since you were ten?
So boring. Stop talking nonsense.
Come on, food's ready.
The broth is perfect, right?
I was known
as the best  ramyeon  maker in my unit.
[both slurp]
I don't know if it was love.
I just needed to protect her
at all costs, you know?
[both slurping]
At first sight, I thought,
"Whoa, she and I are so alike."
I just knew.
So, you loved her since you were seven?
Uh… just eat.
[Wan-do slurping]
-[music concludes]
-[Yeong-do] What?
What do you mean by that?
Forget the special lecture, okay?
How many times do I have to say it?
I asked you to give me
three days' notice, right?
The lecture was scheduled last minute.
Do you think I really want to go?
Hey, you barely see each other.
Don't you feel a little bad for Sang-su?
[Mun-yeong] Of course I feel bad.
That's why I'm calling you,
although I hate doing it.
I mean, come on.
Why else would I be crazy enough
to call you, huh?
[scoffs] Are you serious? What an honor.
Oh, God, I'm fucking thrilled.
Oh, no. Poor Yeong-do.
His life is so very hard.
Stop playing the victim.
You're almost 50 years old. That's low.
The victim, really?
Hey, you're a nuisance.
What? The pity party is over.
Pity party? The fucking audacity.
Every single problem I have…
Good thing we didn't bring Sang-su, right?
[Yeong-do] You've got some fucking nerve…
They wouldn't be fighting if he were here.
[Yeong-do] I'm fine. You calm down.
You think so?
[Yeong-do] Think about our son,
not yourself.
-I'm fishing. How is that a problem?
-Hmm.
How deep are we talking?
[Yeong-do] Forget it. Whatever.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's fine.
-I don't need it… [continues indistinctly]
-How about…
-360 feet?
-[Yeong-do] Why'd you call me
-if you're just gonna do…
-That's deep indeed.
…whatever the hell you want.
-Jeez. God.
-[chuckles softly]
[Yeong-do]
I can't stand hearing your voice.
[Mi-do]  Mom…
QUEENS HAIR SALON
…what if I… what if I die
before Namgung does?
[groans, sighs]
Okay, did you really need to do that?
Why are you trying to jinx it?
And right before your wedding?
-Knock wood!
-Knock, knock! Okay.
As I was telling you…
you never know
what the future holds, right?
You didn't know Dad
would die so young either.
Anyway, if I die
and Namgung outlives me…
I want him to have
this place after I'm gone.
It's my inheritance.
If I die and you don't give it to him,
I'll come back for you.
-Hey!
-[gasps] Why are you raising your voice?
I don't care what you want.
Hoya is getting the whole thing,
so don't get your hopes up, young girl.
-Look at her always counting her chickens.
-[gasps]
How can you do that?
I thought I was the one getting it.
Give it to me
so that I can share with Namgung.
Oh, God. Got three kids and for what, huh?
Hoya is the only one
who cares about me these days.
-[scoffs]
-[soft guitar music playing]
[Suk-hee] He's the one changing
the window screens in the summer.
In winter, he buys insulation covers
so the pipes don't freeze.
He regularly cleans the AC
and checks the boiler.
Even when the rooftop paint peeled off,
Hoya painted it as soon as he heard.
He even came last week and installed
new anti-slip tape on the stairs.
Didn't he do that last year?
He comes every year to do it.
My son replaces it
even if I tell him they're still fine.
[chuckles] He's so sweet.
Whenever Hoya changes the old tape,
it feels like winter is finally here.
Hey.
You should talk to Hoya about this.
You're getting married.
You should ask him to…
Don't mention this to Namgung, all right?
You've got fire in your eyes.
So much anger.
We're Namgung's family.
You and me, Lee Yeong-do…
Lee Sang-su. He has nobody else.
He has no one but us.
If I die,
Namgung gets this place. [groans]
[sighs]
[music concludes]
[Mi-do grunts softly]
What? When did you get here?
Just now.
You kept tossing around.
Hmm. I took a nap earlier.
I think that's why.
Hey, Mi-do.
I know you like being alone
on your dad's anniversary,
so I've always given you space.
But let me stay tonight.
-Would you?
-[sighs]
All right, you can stay with me.
Hmm?
[both exhale]
[hiccups, sighs]
Should we go see a doctor?
[groans softly] If it doesn't go away
by the weekend, I'll go.
-Do you promise?
-Mm. [sighs]
Namgung.
I really want to feel butterflies for you.
And I really want you
to feel them for me too.
[gentle guitar music playing]
[both smooch]
[inhales sharply]
[cell phone vibrating]
-Is that from work?
-I don't care, ignore it.
-[cell phone continues vibrating]
-[both smooch]
-[grunts softly]
-Just answer it, it's bothering me.
No, I don't care.
-[cell phone continues vibrating]
-[breathes deeply]
[sighs]
-Fine, give me a sec.
-Mm.
[cell phone continues vibrating]
[Mi-do sighs]
[Namgung] Good evening, sir.
I'll call them
and get back to you immediately.
-[sighs]
-Yes.
-[line disconnects]
-I'm sorry.
Mm.
-[line rings, connects]
-[Namgung] Sang-hun,
at La Vita's local factory,
they recalled everything
due to high aflatoxin levels.
I'll call their headquarters,
you check on things there.
-Yeah. ASAP.
-[music concludes]
HUNMIN CONFECTIONARY
It won't be easy, but since La Vita
wants to meet personally,
I'll report back after.
-Right. Talk to them and be flexible.
-Yeah.
[sighs]
MIDORI
[Namgung]  Are you awake?
Work is being sorted out.
Texting so you don't worry.
We should go on a trip together
when things calm down.
I know you love Taipei.
Or maybe Hawaii?
It'd be kind of cool, don't you think?
[computer mouse clicking]
Oh, wow.
I thought you'd come after lunch.
Everyone, this is Park Su-a
from Snack Team 4.
She's been assigned to our team today.
We'll be working together.
-Introduce yourself.
-I'm Park Su-a.
Nice to meet you all.
I look forward to collaborating.
I really thought I'd made myself clear
the last time we talked,
but you're quite persistent, Su-a.
Manager Seok Dong-hwan, Jeong Yeon-ho,
Manager Yoon Jae-mun,
Manager Jeong Seok-ho, also Baek Seok-u.
Not to mention Director Yoon,
and most of his executive personnel.
TF Snack Team 3,
your fourth sample tasted different
because you used imported sweet potatoes.
A mistake, I guess.
So from now on, they'll be extra careful
when planning samples.
I mean, whatever date
they absolutely refuse to read to,
that's probably the planned date
to do the switch.
So, the only reason you wanted to talk
is 'cause you want my team's schedule.
I'm asking to be there
when your sample's scheduled.
I know I'm being selfish,
but you can do that much.
Let me handle the rest.
[inhales sharply]
[sighs]
Are you really not…
[inhales deeply]
[sighs] The more I look, the more
you resemble Executive Director Yoon.
-Huh? Wow. That frown is all your father.
-[quirky instrumental music playing]
[squeak sound effect]
[comedic slide whistle sound effect]
Okay, I get it.
Let's pretend you're not related to him.
I'd say you're prickly, that's all.
Let's eat.
We gotta get back to work, right?
It won't interfere with Team 3's work.
Please, the day your manager schedules it,
just let me tag along.
That's too dangerous. I don't think so.
If a scandal like this breaks out,
the company will launch an investigation,
and our new crop-related product releases
would come to a complete standstill.
I'm not crazy enough to be part
of something that'll screw us over.
Your food's getting cold.
[slurping]
-[music concludes]
-But if we release it
under these conditions,
the quality will be inadequate!
We can't get good results in the market.
I'm sure you know that too.
Of course I know it.
But you, Park Su-a, seem to be missing
what's really important.
Our team won't be scheduling
any processes for a while.
I heard that the peperoncino vendor
is having some issues too.
What?
I may look like a nice guy,
but I have a terrible personality
and I'm basically a boomer.
So, I get easily triggered
and I throw fits.
[quirky instrumental music playing]
The problem is that
I'm your direct supervisor as of today.
Can you handle the power imbalance?
[bell dinging sound effect]
[sighs]
-[gasps] Shit. I just can't-- Wait!
-[music concludes]
JAEKANG LAW FIRM
[pages rustling]
[sighs heavily]
[inhales deeply]
-[combination lock wheels clicking]
-[latch clicks]
[soft poignant music playing]
[Seung-ho]
Those words hit hard back then,
and I'd really like
to return the favor now.
You're never going
to make your feature film debut.
You've lost momentum.
You've lost your passion.
That's why you're going
to fade into obscurity.
And now… enjoy my film.
[sniffles]
-[sighs] Why are you following me around?
-[music concludes]
I'm just worried.
Wait, I must not tell lies.
-'Cause I'm curious.
-Crazy.
Hmm.
That face gives you away.
What do you mean?
Don't clench your jaw so much. You're…
embarrassed
and yet holding that emotion in.
[sighs]
You're in no position
to treat me like this.
Just as you're in no position
to be releasing that picture.
[chuckles softly]
You see, you're acting like
you could win this with just one picture.
But that leverage only works
if you're willing
to deal with the outcome.
Can you really deal with the outcome of…
releasing it?
You'll never know unless I do.
I'm completely crazy as you can see.
So think twice before pushing your luck.
-What would you do if I caused trouble?
-Then be my guest.
What? Do you need permission to do it?
[Mi-do sighs]
[intriguing instrumental music playing]
[grunts softly]
[scoffs]
[sighs]
[music fades]
SIM HAE-JU
[line ringing]
[Hae-ju]  Hey there, it's Sim Hae-ju.
I run errands and do it all.
Any updates on Mi-do?
[Hae-ju]  Ah, the cloud server's
much harder to break into.
It has two-factor authentication
and endpoint encryption.
I just tried a brute-force attack
and, uh, got kicked out. It failed.
Then what now?
-[music resumes]
-[Hae-ju]  It's gonna take at least a day.
Two days if you don't want
any logs left over.
But if it's saved on another cloud,
this is pointless too.
Just meet with her and negotiate.
That might be faster.
You think I haven't tried that, huh?
She won't listen to reason.
-She's a nutcase.
-[Hae-ju]  Crazier than you?
Hey, I'm a very reasonable person!
What are you saying? Okay, whatever.
Blow the server up or the account.
Just fix the situation.
Or you're gonna be the one
to blow to pieces, okay?
[Hae-ju]  Hey!
I thought you were reasonable.
[Tae-seung sighs]
Ah, damn it. [inhales deeply]
[music concludes]
-[heavy rain pouring]
-[thunder rumbling]
[suspenseful music playing]
-[lightning cracking]
-[thunder rumbling]
[music rises]
[rapid heavy footsteps approaching]
[Yu-seong] What happened?
-Sir?
-He's already dead.
[gasps]
It's not true.
Tell me you didn't do it.
Did you?
[Chan-hui] It was an accident.
Get out of here for now.
Don't forget the competition.
No, sir. Please.
-[lightning cracking]
-[thunder rumbling]
Ko Yu-seong.
Listen carefully to what I tell you.
-[music builds dramatically]
-[thunder rumbling]
-[lightning cracking]
-Hey, line?
-[music concludes]
[inhales sharply]
CHAN-HUI
-[soft music playing over speakers]
-♪ It's time to start over again ♪
[breathes deeply]
♪ Look out for some… ♪
[sighs]
[man] Work on page 30.
See? It's on page 20 here.
-Uh, but rather than the topic on page 20…
-Yeah?
…this one up here is more in line with
what I've been studying since last…
[Mi-do]  Excitement didn't just fade
from my love life.
[dreamy pop music playing]
[Mi-do]  The realization suddenly hit me.
I can't even remember the last time
my heart actually raced for something.
When did I last feel a spark?
-♪ When I need you someday ♪
-[sighs]
♪ Will you stay the same? ♪
[vocalist singing in Korean]
♪ You're still my easy place ♪
CHAN-HUI
[sighs]
-[vocalist singing in Korean]
-[arcade machine buttons clicking]
[buttons clicking rapidly]
[song continues]
♪ Too fast ♪
[sighs]
♪ But I slow down near you
Till it all feels easy ♪
♪ You make it easy but you don't know ♪
♪ That's why I can finally breathe
'Cause of you ♪
♪ When I need you someday ♪
♪ Will you stay the same? ♪
[vocalist singing in Korean]
♪ You're still my easy place ♪
♪ I still see you ♪
♪ When I close my eyes
And lie in the silence… ♪
[song continues playing indistinctly
over speakers]
[chuckles nervously]
Don't stare, all right?
This is awkward for me too.
Forgot something?
Hmm?
-Like what?
-[scoffs]
-[breathes deeply]
-[song concludes]
-[quirky instrumental music playing]
-[gasps] Ah.
-Mm. Bling Bling app is good.
-Bling Bling? Mm.
-[cell phone camera clicking]
-[gasps]
Hold it. You look so pretty.
-[gasps] Mm.
-[cell phone camera clicking]
Look left. Yeah. Sexy.
[chuckles]
[glasses clink]
[exhales]
It's nice to have a date with you.
I feel nostalgic.
Listen, how about if we go on dates
like this at least once a year?
What do you think?
It builds romantic tension, which is nice.
-Four times.
-Hmm?
Once is not enough.
It's better four times a year.
What? No?
[quirky instrumental music continues]
[both smooching]
[both pant]
[both smooch]
-[hiccups]
-[Namgung grunts]
[rapid footsteps receding]
[music concludes]
[Mi-do gags]
Hey, Mi-do. [grunts softly]
[doctor] I reviewed your test results.
Your CT scan and X-rays came back normal.
It seems to be indigestion.
How long has she been hiccupping?
It's been about a week or so, I guess.
-Right?
-Uh-huh. [hiccups]
[doctor] Stress is often a trigger
for this kind of thing.
If it doesn't stop by this week,
you'll need to come back to the ER.
Okay. Thank you.
[hiccups]
[sighs heavily]
YUSEONG UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
You should get a health checkup.
Did you have one last year?
Don't overreact.
Didn't you hear the doctor? [hiccups]
Book it now. Okay, I'll do it.
Uh, wait, wait a minute.
What do you think about this hospital?
-[woman moaning sound effect]
-[smooching sound effect]
-God!
-What? Is it bad?
Is this a joke to you?
What the hell are you…
What? Say it. What? Tell me. Huh?
[sighs] Fine. Let's not argue.
[scoffs] Really?
[sighs]
-[sighs]
-[playful instrumental music playing]
You really brought that up
at the ER, love?
But the hospital said
it wasn't a big deal, love. Hmm?
And I think this is more important
for us, love.
I just wish
we could do this naturally, love.
We agreed to try, love.
You promised, love.
Okay, love.
-But get a checkup, love.
-Okay, I will, love.
[grunts softly]
-Do we have to keep doing this?
-It actually worked.
Ending each sentence with "love" works.
It forces us to act cute,
-so it tones down the intensity.
-[groans softly]
Anyway, you promised.
-You'll have a checkup?
-Yeah, got it.
[music concludes]
By the way, your mom called me today.
She said she's clearing out
the rooftop room.
She told us to take whatever we want.
-Shall we go?
-Our rooftop? Really? Why?
QUEENS HAIR SALON
[cell phone chimes]
Hey, Namgung.
I just got here a second ago.
Yeah, I'll start cleaning it out.
There shouldn't be much.
Yeah. Okay, call me
when you get off work. Mm-hmm.
[sighs]
Wow.
-It feels like it's been an eternity.
-[gentle guitar music playing]
[Mi-do]
I feel like we need something really big
to happen the moment they walk in.
But doing that would only end up
making the shoot even longer,
and we'd need a lot more time
to prepare for it.
-If you need it, you should do it.
-I should, right?
-That's exactly what I thought. [chuckles]
-Taste this, Mi-do.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, let me try.
-[vocalist singing in Korean]
-[slurps]
-Is it good?
-It's really good.
-Is it? [slurps]
-Mm-hmm.
Mm! Mm!
-It's so late. See you later.
-[Namgung] Bye.
-Oh, Mi-do.
-Yeah?
-[Namgung] Here, take this.
-[gasps]
-Good luck. Mm-hmm.
-[mumbling indistinctly]
-Mm. Mm!
-[smooches]
-Mm!
-See ya.
What kind of performance…
[sighs] Never mind.
Why do I keep…
[vocalist continues singing in Korean]
-[kisses]
-[grunts softly]
Don't do that.
I'm busy right now, honey.
I should explain that.
-[gasps]
-[kisses]
Hey! Hey! Wait a second! [giggles]
[echoing]  I said no! Stop it!  [giggles]
[sighs] Hmm.
[vocalist continues singing in Korean]
[water spraying]
-[music concludes]
-[machine rumbling]
[pants, grunts softly]
[sighs]
[scoffs]
Listen, this is bullying, you know?
Bullying, really?
Uh, the word is "exploitation."
Two days ago,
I analyzed three years of survey data.
Yesterday, I did a full run-through
of all peperoncino suppliers,
and today, overtime for shipments.
This is exploitation.
Right, so Park Su-a catches
on fast, doesn't she?
[scoffs]
-So you admit this is wrong, don't you?
-I'm not happier than you, Su-a.
But you're gonna keep…
focusing on your weird theories
unless I give you tasks to distract you.
[playful instrumental music playing]
Two days ago, you were snooping around
raw material specs and guidelines.
Unit price adjustments
and partner changes yesterday and today.
You're checking if box lot numbers
and shipping labels can be rigged.
And if so,
who inside the farm is helping out?
Is that what you were looking for?
I hate workplace exploitation too.
It's despicable.
But what can I do?
Your hero complex
is interfering with work,
so I have no other choice.
[music rises]
I'm not asking for your help anymore.
And I won't cause any more trouble.
But…
how about you let me handle
the sample processing schedule?
It's just that…
I struggle with your ideas.
Oh, my God!
-Should I tell the vice president?
-[music concludes]
I'm curious, are you trying
to get promoted?
Are you aiming for director?
What, do you think I have no ambition?
Just don't let my ambitions
silence my conscience
because of your actions.
Don't let it get in the way of work.
-Hey, where are you going?
-Playing hooky.
[sighs]
SWEET POTATO
-[forklift truck beeping]
-[quirky piano music playing]
[sniffs]
Oh, my. My goodness.
Did you… Did you do all this alone?
Yeah. Uh, where's Namgung?
I don't know.
I guess he must be with my husband
at the senior center.
And they're…
playing. Solid gaming.
Game of cards. [grunts]
Hate when he does that. [groans]
We're shorthanded as it is,
but he's playing around.
-Anyway, thank you so much.
-[chuckles awkwardly]
Whoo! You're pretty,
but also a hard worker. Oh!
Just look at all these.
You did a really good job.
[chuckles]
-[sword drawing sound effect]
-[music concludes]
[Mi-do sighs]
[inhales, hums softly]
Hmm,  Slam Dunk,  where is it?
[inhales sharply]
Where is…
[sighs] I can't find it.
Huh?
[grunts, sighs]
[grunts]
[cell phone vibrating]
ALUMINUM CAN BASTARD
That shitty lawyer.
-[cell phone continues vibrating]
-[grunts]
-[bookshelf creaks]
-Whoa!
-[bookshelf crashes]
-[Mi-do groans]
[train rumbling]
-[poignant instrumental music playing]
-[groans, pants]
[panting, grunting]
[grunts]
[pants]
[groans]
-[cord snaps]
-[yelps, gasps]
[panting heavily]
[ceiling light creaking]
-[pants]
-[Tae-seung over phone]  Hello.
-[continues panting]
-[Tae-seung]  Director?
ALUMINUM CAN BASTARD
[Tae-seung]  Ms. Lee.
-[continues panting]
-[music concludes]
[birds chirping]
HOW TO STOP HICCUPS
HICCUPS FOR OVER 3 DAYS.
SHOULD I SEE A DOCTOR?
[cows mooing]
[snores, smacks lips]
[scoffs]
[Su-a inhales deeply]
[sighs]
[gasps softly]
Oh, my God. What?
I'm worried.
Right now on your head…
there's a huge spider the size of my hand.
-[gasps]
-No, no, stay still.
-It could be a poisonous spider.
-Huh?
In the army during training…
my partner got bitten
by a poisonous spider.
-Did he die?
-[scoffs]
He didn't die, however…
[inhales, groans] Do…
Do you have a tissue? I'll take it off.
[soft instrumental music playing]
[gasps] Are you crazy?
You said it could be poisonous.
[chuckles softly]
[scoffs]
[clears throat]
Jokes like this aren't funny.
Don't ever do it again.
[chuckles softly]
What are you waiting for? Kill it!
Don't be so cruel with it.
Spiders are great bugs.
[sighs]
It was able to survive
all the way until November.
How could you kill…
such an impressive guy?
[music concludes]
[grunts]
[door closes]
[ceiling light creaking]
[scoffs]
-[electricity crackling]
-Oh.
-[electricity crackles]
-[soft eerie musical sting]
[sighs] Director.
Are you happy to see me here?
Cut the greetings. Move the bookshelf.
[inhales deeply, sighs]
Oh, but wait.
If I help you to move it,
will you sign the settlement for me?
[hiccups]
And surrender the pic you saved
to the cloud account?
What?
So, no. Maybe it's better
if I just let you die here.
[inhales deeply, sighs]
[scoffs] Did you hear that?
I was thinking out loud.
I've seen a surveillance camera
in the store.
It caught you walking in here.
Plus, you were my last phone call.
Hmm.
-I really don't care.
-[intriguing instrumental music playing]
I'll say that when I got here,
you were already dead.
-[chuckles]
-Aluminum can shithead.
Trash that won't decompose
for at least 200 years.
[scoffs] I'm not planning
on living that long, so…
Anyhow…
[inhales sharply]
…there's that. [exhales]
And I'd say it'll last…
-[electricity crackles]
-…another ten minutes before it falls.
So you must decide soon.
Just get lost. [sighs]
-[Tae-seung] Won't you regret it?
-[scoffs softly]
[music fades]
-Okay. [sighs] I'll leave you to it.
-[music resumes]
-Fucking nutcase. [sighs]
-[footsteps receding]
-[breathes deeply]
-[door closes]
-[sighs]
-[music concludes]
Hey, you. Good job today.
-Here. These are for you, young lady.
-Oh.
-[chuckles]
-Thank you, ma'am.
-Where's Namgung?
-Huh?
Uh, he mentioned he had
to check the sorting station.
Did Namgung give you a cut?
He took everyone to the cleaners.
He's so smooth!
[farm owner's wife]
Now we know where he actually was.
Ah, so you were at the senior center too.
[farm owner] Jeez, why would you bring up
the senior center?
-[groans]
-Shut it. You're always there.
It's all over your GPS history.
Don't you think I didn't know?
-It's just senior, senior, senior.
-The GPS route.
Uh… Oh, keep arguing.
It's all right.
-Huh? What?
-Huh?
[both continue arguing indistinctly]
[Su-a]
If I check the transport driver's GPS,
I might be able
to find out where the switch happens.
[slow intriguing music playing]
[farm owner's wife] Oh, hi, Mr. Oh.
You left the car running.
We'll load all the goods on the truck.
Go ahead and rest in the break room.
-You look exhausted.
-Yeah, thank you. Appreciate it.
[sighs]
-[cutlery clinking]
-[music fades]
YANGJIN SWEET POTATO SORTING FACILITY
-[funky intriguing music playing]
-[forklift truck beeping]
[music intensifies]
[gasps]
RECENT ROUTES
[tractor door opens, closes]
[engine rumbling]
[music concludes]
[engine rumbling fades]
[breathes deeply]
[door opens]
You must get told
that you're stubborn a lot.
No, wait. [sighs]
They probably just say that you're crazy.
[sighs]
Just sign the settlement, Director.
It's better than dying, right?
So what about your family?
What about your boyfriend?
You just broke up with that guy
and are already back together with him.
And now you're planning a wedding.
-[Mi-do sobbing]
-[poignant instrumental music playing]
You're crying?
[sobbing]
I figured it out a while ago.
You really love him, huh?
[Mi-do] I think it would actually
be better for Namgung if I die first.
I'm the main reason he sacrificed it all.
That makes me even more curious.
-[sobs]
-I'll ask once more. Here we go.
Tell me you're gonna sign.
[breathes deeply] Shit.
[breathes deeply]
[inhales deeply] Okay.
You've earned this victory.
[grunts softly]
[grunts]
-[electricity crackles]
-[cord snaps]
[glass shatters]
[pants]
-[music rises]
-[continues panting]
[gasps] You're bleeding.
[pants]
[music concludes]
Won't you eat?
Traffic will be bad later, so eat now.
[munches, slurps]
Why were you there earlier?
-You better answer.
-What are you talking about?
-Are you hallucinating?
-[scoffs]
[inhales deeply]
-[slurps]
-You pretended you weren't involved.
But you were playing detective
behind my back.
-I've never done that.
-Oh.
I guess you're still waffling.
I guess I had you wrong.
Listen, if I knew you played so safe,
I never would have asked
a coward like you.
So I'm sorry.
[slurps]
-[cutlery clinking]
-From now on, I'll handle this alone.
So back off and stay out.
-[cutlery clinking]
-Can you send me the picture?
Okay. I get it.
So now, I'll go and take one myself.
If I was a nuisance to you, I apologize.
[Namgung] Just sit down.
[soft instrumental music playing]
I speak politely,
and you cross the line to scare me.
For real?
[scoffs] Seriously, this is unbelievable.
-Hey.
-[sighs]
Deok-sun, you've grown a lot.
You're saying you don't like needles?
SANGJIN UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
-I have an underlying condition.
-What do you mean?
Well, I'm scared of needles, so…
Uh, they said
it's only like five stitches.
It only hurts
while it gets numb, don't worry.
I don't care if it's for one second,
stitches are not for me.
[gasps, exhales]
Just disinfect it and put a bandage on it,
and give me a week of antibiotics.
Uh, the thing is,
if the wound doesn't heal properly,
it could become necrotic or cause sepsis.
I'm sorry,
but my advice is to get stitches.
[music rises]
Well, this one was even worse.
But they just cleaned it
and gave me amoxicillin.
-Please, let's just do that.
-[sighs]
EMERGENCY ROOM
-[music concludes]
-Do you think this will make me settle?
I really doubt you will.
You wouldn't even do it
to save your own life.
-Then why won't you let them treat you?
-I hate needles, I told you.
-I have a trauma with them.
-You expect me to… [hiccups]
[sighs] …to believe all that?
Ever had something shoved
under your nails?
-I'm not sure what you mean.
-It's painful as hell.
I grew up in an orphanage,
and the director used to do that
to punish all of us.
To avoid getting caught in audits,
he used an untraceable method.
But more than the pain,
the waiting was the worst.
Waiting for my turn was way scarier.
[scoffs] Don't look at me like that.
I turned out pretty well,
even growing up as an orphan.
Pretty obvious. Don't you think?
That's just bullshit, right?
You almost bought it.
-Hey, don't-- [sighs] This idiot.
-[cell phone vibrating]
-Hello?
-[Namgung]  Where are you?
What happened in here? Did you do this?
-Are you hurt?
-Uh-uh, I didn't get hurt. [sighs]
-The bookshelf fell, that's all.
-[sighs]
Babe, I really gotta go, okay?
-Hey-- Uh…
-[line disconnects]
Bill the car repairs fee… [hiccups]
…and today's hospital bill together.
We can't meet
the settlement terms you requested.
No studio in their right mind
would ever agree to that.
Instead… I believe I have grounds
to negotiate for your return.
At this moment, the studio has officially
appointed Director Kim Jung-man
as your successor.
You know the guy. From college, right?
I can dig into his past
and find dirt. Hmm.
Heard he's got a gambling history.
I know a few entertainment reporters.
Just tell me that you approve it,
and I'll get to work right away.
No. Don't.
Excuse me?
[inhales deeply]
-There's more to it, isn't there?
-What?
[scoffs] I found it strange for a while.
All you asked for
was double your directing fee.
I mean, anyone would ask
to be reinstated as director.
-But you, on the other hand…
-Because your methods are cheap and dirty.
God, they're really sad.
-[pensive instrumental music playing]
-Ah.
Interesting.
Director, can I give you
a crazy suggestion?
No, don't bother.
[scoffs] Keep holding out
and you'll break.
So why hold out like this?
I'm not only talking about the settlement.
What about what happened on that rooftop?
Can't you compromise just once?
You seemed ready to die.
[scoffs] Of course,
I looked into your background.
It never ends well for you.
[music rises]
[Tae-seung] What's the point
of having all that talent?
You have to learn when to compromise.
That's how you survive.
Oh. Like you, I suppose?
I looked into your background, too.
You stick by Seo Ju-hyeok,
and you're quite famous
for giving him absolutely everything.
[scoffs]
[Mi-do] From finding clients
to prepping trials.
And if that wasn't enough,
you manage his personal life.
You do whatever Seo Ju-hyeok tells you to.
Is that so bad?
I just sell my skills to the person
who values them the most.
But I work myself sick every day
just to earn that.
Don't you think doing that is really sad?
-Kind of pathetic?
-How can anyone walk on only paved roads?
You walk down enough rough roads,
you step in a little mud now and then.
That's life.
But Seo Ju-hyeok walks on paved roads,
thanks to you.
Can I give you a crazy suggestion?
Stop working for the highest bidder.
Work for someone
who treats you like a person.
You see, no one considers
their dog their peer at work.
[scoffs]
-A dog, really?
-You're right. Dog is not accurate.
You're a son of a bitch
your owner could toss aside any day.
[music softens]
[scoffs, laughs]
[inhales deeply, sighs]
[sighs] You're truly funny.
[pensive instrumental music continues]
See if you can keep up the act.
[whispers] I'm just joking.
[laughs] Oh, did I scare you?
It might be worth considering
a return to directing.
I'm willing to do this
by any means necessary.
But only if you want to. [chuckles]
Fucking nutcase. [sighs]
[gasps softly]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[music concludes]
Honestly, Park Deok-sun,
how is she exactly the same?
-[scoffs]
-[keypad beeping]
-Mi-do, you're home?
-Yeah.
Tteokbokki  will be ready in a minute.
[both chuckle softly]
-[poignant piano music playing]
-[breathes deeply]
[breathes shakily]
Mi-do, what is it?
Oh? Your hiccups are gone.
No, they'll come back soon.
No, they're really gone.
-Huh?
-Nothing ever worked before.
-What changed?
-Good question.
They stopped for real.
[cell phone vibrates]
ALUMINUM CAN BASTARD
PARK SU-A
[dramatic rock music playing]
THANK YOU TO KIM DA-HUIN, PARK SUNG-HOON,
AND NAM DA-REUM
FOR THEIR SPECIAL APPEARANCE
[vocalist singing in Korean]
[Su-a]
I wanted the whole world to hate you.
[sobbing]
[Namgung]  Acting like
we don't even know each other?
-Uh, yeah.
-Wait, "yeah"?
ANY SPARE MONEY?
I NEED TWO MILLION WON MORE THIS MONTH.
-[Tae-seung]  Go back to directing?
-[Mi-do]  Is that an option?
-[Tae-seung]  Of course.
-Yes! Right?
-[Namgung]  I don't think I can do it.
-Huh?
[Namgung]  This is not a shonen manga,
you know?
Please, just don't give up on your art.
It really suits you.
Threaten him again,
and I swear that I will kill you.
I might just scare him too.
It'd be quite entertaining.
-♪ Everything feels the same… ♪
-[music concludes]